PULL
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
A demon's crept into
our everyday life
It's about to take away
something precious
Our peace has already
crumbled long ago
So casually, so nonchalantly
It's taken from us
before we know it
If we want it back,
now's the chance
With the sharpness of
the piercing arrow
The beauty of two souls united
Wherever you go, chase you
Whenever, chase you
I will chase you
Nowhere to escape
Start running, I will chase you
Tomorrow, chase you
My fists will be the one
to show you
Tenacity decides
who will win or lose
So I chase you
EPISODE 26
ROSHAM BOY IS HERE!
"ROSHAMBO" FAN.
WILL PLAY "ROSHAMBO" AT ANY CHANCE.
PLAYS "SCISSORS" FIRST.
OPEN
CANNOT ATTACK ROHAN KISHIBE.
I CANNOT ATTACK ROHAN KISHIBE.
I CAN ATTACK ROHAN KISHIBE.
5 MATCHES
MATCH 1
MATCH 2
MATCH 3
MATCH 4
MATCH 5
HEAVEN'S DOOR
ROHAN
KEN
5 MATCHES
MENACING
CRASH
I WILL RESCUE ROHAN FROM DANGER.
I WILL TURN MYSELF INVISIBLE AND
MAKE THE KID'S HAND INTO "ROCK".
BOOM
PFFT
DASH
EPISODE 27
I'M AN ALIEN